that avil made a podcast to delox And
que la avil aó un podcast al delox Y
then in that debate well they throw several
entonces en ese debate pues tiran varias
barbs not to Dalas with the subject of the
pullas no al Dalas con el tema de los
contracts Haha the contracts there are no
contratos Jaja los contratos no hay
people who make contracts I don't know how much And
gente que hace contrato no sé cuánto Y
look, Dallas came to my channel the other day
fíjate que el Dallas vino el otro día a
and told me that Dallas when he
mi canal y me só que Dallas cuando le
did the podcast to delo no Or just in case he
hizo el podcast a delo no O por si acaso
recorded something that is also a thing of
grabó una cosa que también son cosa de
having a bald ass Not that you record the
tener el culo pelado No que grabes la
interview just in case you get it pure
entrevista por si acaso la te marip pura
And then he recorded delox and the friend
Y entonces los grabó a delox y al amigo
talking badly about Abi The friend who is the
hablando mal de Abi El amigo que es el
editor Sleeps with her the positions he made
editor se Acosta con ella las posturas
calling her a [ __ ] [ __ ] all
que hizo diciéndole put todas
these things no Well then Dalas tells her
estas cosas no Bueno pues le dice Dalas
Abi Here I have the recording in case you
Abi Aquí tengo la graba por si lo
want to listen to what these
quieres escuchar lo que dic de ti esta
people that you are collaborating with now
gente con la que estás colaborando ahora
and the other one that you have slept with say about you
y el otro con el que te has acostado
telling all the positions that you have
contando todas las posturas que has
done and all the things that you have done
hecho y todas las cosas que has hecho
calling you warra I don't know I know how much Look if
llamándote warra no sé sé cuanto Mira si
instead of laughing the
en vez de reírse el contrato de
confidentiality contract had taken an example
confidencialidad hubiera cogido ejemplo
then Abi would have  50,000 turkeys
pues ahora Abi tendría 50,000 pavitos